Guide to the Georg Kreisel Papers SC0136
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Correspondence
  - Hathematical Reviews (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Royal Society (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - World Congress of Philosophy (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Unidentified Articles (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Aristotle Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Baldwin, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Barendregt, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Barwise, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Beeson, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Bibel, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Bokser, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Boolos, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Cagnoni, Donatella - Anthology, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Cappelletti, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Cassells, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Cellucci, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Crick, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Culmer, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Daykin, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - del Franco, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - de Ligne, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Delzell, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Dragolin, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Dreben, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Dyson, Verena, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Engeler, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Ershov, Andrei, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Ershov, Y. L., 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Feferman, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Felscher, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Ferrabee, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Friedman, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Gandy, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Girard, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Goad, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Godel Obituary, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Godel Obituary (Rudolf Godel), 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Gordeev, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Graz, Austria, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Hacking, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Harrington, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Herre, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Hlawka, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Hyland, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Jaeger, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Jost, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Kaufmann-Buhler, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Ketonen, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Kuiper, Nicolaas, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Lacan, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Lam, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Lenstra, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Lifschitz, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Luckhardt, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - MacIntyre, Angus, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Madman, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Martin-Lof, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Mazur, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Mints, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Motchane, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Murdoch, Iris, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - Mycielski, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Nedo, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Nepeivode, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Nerodi, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Odifreddi, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Parikh, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Penrose, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Pohlers, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Pour-El, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Prawitz, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Prestle, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Rautenberg, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Reznikoff, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Riebenboim, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Renee, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Rogers, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Roquette, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Royal Society, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Sabbagh, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Sachs, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Schein, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Schmerl, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Schmidt, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Scott, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Shepherdson, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Simpson, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Sinaceur, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Smorynski, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Solavay, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Speck, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Specker, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Statman, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Stavi, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Stepanov, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Stone, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Strauss, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Sundholm, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Suppes, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Takeuti, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Alusio, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - American Scientist, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Aristotle, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Bandgert, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Cellucci, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Christman, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Crick, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Crossley, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - del Franco, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Delzell, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Engeler, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Friedman, H., 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Girard, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Graz, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Guillaume, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Hirzbruche, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Hlawka, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Jaeger, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Jost, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Kingman, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Kuiper, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - L-E, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Luckhardt, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Madman, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Mazur, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Hints, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Olifreddi, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Prawitz, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Sabbagh, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Sacks, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Schein, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Schudenberg, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Scott, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Simpson, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Statman, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Suppes, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Takeuti, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Toelstra, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Tosie, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Vail, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Van Heijnoort, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Vogel, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Weingartner, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Wojtylak, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Zinciviev, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Zucker, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Evaluating, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Evaluation-Delzell, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Lecture two texts, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Proof theory, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Publications, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Use of lectures, 1979 Jul - 1980 May (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Aershov, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Barendregt, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Beeson, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bibel, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Cassel, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Cellucci, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Coates, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Crick, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Crossley, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Diesen, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - del Franco, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Deligne, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Delzell, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Dummat, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Engeler, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Eishov, Y. L., 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Friedman, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Frolich, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Girard, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Goad, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Graham, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Guillaume, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Haller, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Hasenjager, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Hirzebruch, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Hlawka, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Howard, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Hyland, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Iris Murdoch, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Jacquch, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Jaeger, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Jensen, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Jones, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Jost, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Ketonen, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Kleene, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Kock, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Krause, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Lacan, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Leivant, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Lenstra, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Levy, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Lifschitz, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Luckhardt, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - MacIntyre, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - MacLane, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Madman, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Makovsky, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Marek, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Mazur, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Meyer, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Mints, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Mittelstaedt, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Morscher, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Mundici, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Murdoch, Iris, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Odifreddi, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Piatelli, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Pourel, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Prawitz, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Prestel, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Rabin, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Riebenboim, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Royal Society, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Sabbagh, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Sacks, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Schein, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Schimanovic, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Schmerl, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - (Dana) Scott, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - (Philip) Scott, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Sheperdson, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Simpson, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Sinaceur, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Smith, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Smorynski, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Solovay, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Speck, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Specker, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Statman, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Stcpanov, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Sundholm, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Suppes, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Takeuti, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Toelstra, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Van den Dries, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Van Heijnoort, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Weingartner, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Witt, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Winternitz, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Wojtylak, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Zucker, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - American Scientist Review, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - First Versions Unpublished Papers, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Letters of Evaluation, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Letters of recommendation, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Publications-Draft of Publications, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Unpublished Lectures, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Unpublished Notes, 1980 Jun - 1981 Mar (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Barendregt (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Cellucci (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Chreneau (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Crick (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Dawson (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - del Franco (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Delzell (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Dyson (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Feferman (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Friedman (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Friedrich (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Girard (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Goldfarb (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Guillaume (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Haller (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Halmos (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Howard (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Jost (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Kaufman-Buhler (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Krause (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Kuiper (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Lambek (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Lopez-Escobar (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Luckhardt (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - MacIntyre (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Madman (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Makinson (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Mints (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Morley (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Morscher (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Murdoch (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Parikh (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Peters (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Prawitz (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Robinson (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Royal Society (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Sabbagh (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Schmetterer (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Schwichtenberg (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Scott, Dana (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Simpson (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Smith (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Speck (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Spencer (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Statman (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Stepanou (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Suppes (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Takeuti (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Toelstra (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Van Dahlen (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Van den Dries (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Van Heijnoort (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Wilkie (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Wojtylak (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Zilber (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Zucker (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Letters of Evaluation (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Unpublished Notes (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Adams (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Aristotle (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Barendregt (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Burgess (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Cassel (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Cellucci (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Cilber (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Coates (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Cooper (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Crick (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - del Franco (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Deligne (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Delzell (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Engeler (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Ershou (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Feferman (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Fens tad (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Friedman (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Girard (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Goad (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Guillarme (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Howard (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Hylend (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - International Congress of Mathematicians, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Jock (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Jost (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Kaufmann-Buhler (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Keisler (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Kleene (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Kuiper (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Lacan (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Lopez-Escobar (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Luckhardt (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - McIntyre (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Madmen (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Mazer (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Mintz (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Mitter Strass (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Morscher (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Murdoch (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Mycielski (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Myhill (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Nedo (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Perry (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Peters (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Piattell-Palmarina (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Pour-El (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Prawitz (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Prestell (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Royal Society (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Sabbagh (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Sacks (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Schutte (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Schwichtenberg (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Scott (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Simpson (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Smith (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Smithies (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Smorynski (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Statman (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Sumdholm (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Suppes (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Takeuti (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Troelstra (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Van Dalon (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Van den Dries (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Van Heij enoort (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Weingartner (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Wilkie (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Wojtylak (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Zassenhaus (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Zucker (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Anellis, Irving H., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Arnon, Dennis, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Alan, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Barendregt, H., 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Bellin, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Buff, H.W., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Cassels, J.W.S., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Cellucci, C., 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Craig, William, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Daykin, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - del Franco, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Deligne, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Delzell, Charles, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Enderton, Herbert B., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Engeler, E., 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Epstein, Richard L., 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Ershov, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Feferman, Sol, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Friedman, Harvey, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Girard, Jean-Yves, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Herre, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Hintikka, Jaakko, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Howard, William A., 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Hsia, J.S., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Kaufmann-Buhler, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Keister, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Krause, Ralph M., 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Lenstra, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Luckhardt, H., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - MacIntyre, Angus, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - MacIntyre, Angus, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Madison, Gene, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Mate, Attila, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Mathias, Adrian, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Mints, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Moore, Gregory, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Morscher, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Murdoch, Iris, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Mycielski, Jan, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Nedo, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Peters, Klaus, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Piatelli-Palmarini, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Poland, William, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Pour-El, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Prestel, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Sabbagh, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Scedrov, Andrej, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Schmerl, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Scott, Dana, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Scott, Philip, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Shapiro, Stewart, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Sheperdson, J.C., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Shore, Richard A., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Sinaceur, Hourya, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Smith, Rick, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Smorynski, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Statman, Richard, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Stavi, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Stern, Jacques, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Sundholm, G., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Suppes, Patrick, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Takeuti, G., 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Troelstra, A.S., 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Van Benthem, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Van den Dries, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Van den Hoesen, Gerrit, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Van Heijenoort, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Weingartner, Paul, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Wilkie, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Wojcicki, Ryszard, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Wojtylak, P., 1982 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Wu, Wen-Tsin, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Yasugi, Mariko, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Zassenhaus, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Early Drafts (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Evaluations (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Evaluations (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Godel Obituary (Correspondence with John Dawson), 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Godel Obituary (Correspondence with Stephen Kleene), 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Godel Obituary (Correspondence with the staff of the Royal Society), 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Advanced Study, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Madmen, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Royal Society, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Unpublished Lectures (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Unpublished Seminar Notes (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Adams, 1982 Dec - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Anellis, 1982 Jun - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Baez, 1982 Jun - Dec (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Baker, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Benacerraf, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Berlin, 1982 Nov (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Brunner, 1982 Sep - Nov (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Casari, 1982 Oct (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Cassels, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Cellucci, 1982 Sep - Nov (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Coates, 1982 Oct - Nov (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Crabbe (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Crick, 1982 Jul - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Culik, 1982 Dec - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Dawson, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - del Franco, 1982 Jul - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Deligne, 1982 Nov (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Delzell, 1982 May - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Dumett, 1982 Dec (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Engeler, 1982 Jul - Dec (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Ershov, 1982 Nov (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Feferman, 1982 Dec (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Friedman, 1982 Nov (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Girard, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Godel, 1982 Sep - Dec (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Guad, 1982 Jul -Nov (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Gurevich, 1982 Dec - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Hintikka, 1982 Aug (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Hlawka, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Howard, 1982 Jun - Dec (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Hubner, 1982 Jul - Aug (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Hyland, 1982 Jun - Dec (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Jockusch, 1982 Jul (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Kalman, 1978 Apr - Dec (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Kleene, 1982 Aug - Dec (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Krause, 1982 Dec (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Kuiper, 1982 Aug - Nov (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Lenstra, 1982 May - Nov (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Longo, 1982 Nov (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1982 Oct - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Luckhardt, 1982 Jun - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - MacIntyre, 1982 Jun - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Mason, 1982 Nov (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Mate, 1982 Jun (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Mazur, 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Mellis, 1982 Sep - Oct (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Miller, 1982 Jul - Sep (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Mints, 1982 Nov - 1983 Jan (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Mittelstrass, 1982 Jul - Sep (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Morscher, 1982 Jul (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Murdoch, 1982 Jun - Dec (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Nedo, 1982 Oct - Dec (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Perry, 1982 Jun - Jul (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Peters, 1982 Aug - Dec (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Piatelli-Palmarini, 1982 Jul - Dec (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Popham, 1982 Aug (Box 43, Folder 5)